republicwireless.com 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy – Republic Wireless

Republic Wireless Inc. (“Republic Wireless” or “we”), provides wireless communications solutions. To learn more about Republic Wireless, please see “How can you contact us?” below.

We make the security and confidentiality of the personal information that you provide to us a top priority.

This policy applies to our members in the United States and to visitors to our Web sites and mobile applications, including [ _republicwireless.com_](https://republicwireless.com/). Please read our Privacy Policy carefully.

Republic Wireless may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify our community members about material changes to this Privacy Policy by either sending a notice to the email address you provide to us or by placing a prominent notice on our Web sites.

**What Information Do We Collect from You?**

**General**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web sites or communicate with us in any other way. This includes information that identifies you (“personal information”), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal and email addresses, user name(s) and password(s), if applicable. We also may request information about your communications needs and preferences. You can choose not to provide information, but we may require some information about you to use our Web sites and/or services. We also may require some personal information to answer your questions or conduct other transactions on our Web sites. When you contact us, we may monitor or record the communication or keep a record of it to help us train employees and provide customer service.

We do not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties so they can serve advertisements to you.

**Information Automatically Collected Due to Use of Our Wireless Services**

We collect information about our wireless services that you use, including network traffic data, call records, websites visited, applications and features used, service options chosen, mobile and device number(s) and other similar information. We collect and use data regarding your mobile device location for a variety of purposes as described below. We also may collect and use mobile usage information and other information for certain business and marketing reports as described below. We may automatically measure and monitor network performance and the performance of your Internet connection to improve your, or our, overall service levels. We also may access information about your mobile device or device settings to provide customized support or to install or suggest specific applications or services that you use or are necessary for your use of certain services we provide to you.

**Other Information Automatically Collected**

We also automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit our Web sites. For example, we collect session data, including your IP address, Web browser software, and referring Web site. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as content viewed and pages visited. This information also may permit us to identify users associated with multiple devices used to access our sites or services.

We may use cookies for automated data collection. Cookies are small data text files that, if your Web browser permits, can be stored on your computer’s hard drive. Republic Wireless and its Web sites use cookies:

  * To help us recognize your Web browser as a previous visitor and save and remember any preferences set while your Web browser visited our Web sites. For example, if you register on our Web sites, we may use cookies to remember your registration information so you do not need to log into our Web sites each time you visit. We also may save your password in a cookie, if you checked the box entitled “Save this password for automatic sign-in” (or other similar words).

  * To help us customize the content, Web site experience, and advertisements provided to you on our Web sites and on other Web sites across the Internet. For example, when you access a web page, a cookie automatically recognizes your Web browser as you navigate on the Internet and presents you with information and advertising based on your apparent interests.

  * To help measure and research the effectiveness of the features, offerings, advertisements, and email communications (by determining which emails you open and act upon) of our Web sites.

Our Web sites also may use Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or Web bugs). These Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that we place in the code of a Web page. Web beacons allow us to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within our Web sites to another, deliver or communicate with cookies, understand whether you have come to our Web sites from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party Web site, and improve the performance of our Web sites. We also may allow our service providers to use Web beacons to help us understand which emails recipients have opened and track the visitor traffic on our Web sites.

As noted above, we may use these technologies to serve interest-based ads. Many of the advertisements you see on our Web sites are served by Republic Wireless or its service providers and may be based on our collection of data as described herein. However, we also allow third parties to collect information about your online activities through cookies and other technologies, and they may do so over time and across different websites. These third parties include advertising networks and our business partners, who collect information when you view or interact our site or services, our ads, or ads you see on our sites or services. We do not have access to or control cookies or other technologies these third parties may use to collect information about your interests; our Privacy Policy does not cover either these third parties or their information practices.

We also receive and use your mobile device location to provide our wireless voice and data services, emergency services, and location- based applications and services offered by us and third parties, including mapping, navigation, weather, mapping and other applications or tools. Wireless applications and services offered by us and third parties also use mobile device location data. We may use mobile usage information and other information for certain business and marketing reports. This information includes the location of your device, your use of our products and services, and other demographic and interest information obtained by us from other sources. We may use this information to prepare aggregated business and marketing reports that we may use ourselves or share with others for their use, but which do not personally identify you. We also may share location information with other companies in a way that does not personally identify you.

For more information about managing cookies or our use of data we collect automatically, please review “What choices do you have regarding the collection and use of your information?” below.

**Information from Other Sources**

We also may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners and third parties and add it to other information about you. For example, if you visit [ _republicwireless.com_](https://republicwireless.com/)  by “clicking-through” from a site operated by one of our business partners, and you have registered with that partner, then the partner may share with us information about you that you have provided to that partner. For example, we may receive your contact information and demographic information. If you access third party services, such as social media services, through our Web sites, we also may collect information such as your user name, password, and other information made available to us through those third party services. We also may obtain from consumer reporting agencies information about you that helps us with customer authentication and related decisions. We also may obtain additional information about you from outside companies that collect information, including demographic and interest data. We also may obtain contact information and other marketing lead information from third parties, which we may add to other information about you that we maintain.

**Information About Others**

If you have the opportunity to provide contact information for other people or businesses through our Web sites, you should obtain their consent before you provide their personal information to us.

**How Do We Use Your Information?**

Republic Wireless may use the information we collect about you for a variety of purposes, including:

  * The registration and management of your account, including for billing purposes, the delivery and maintenance of products or services, assistance with service-related issues or questions, and the facilitation of your access to and use of our Web sites;

  * Communication with you, including to provide information about Republic Wireless and invitations from Republic Wireless;

  * Responses to your questions and comments, or other customer service;

  * Business and usage analytics, such as measurement of your interest in our products, services, and Web sites, as well as the improvement, management and protection of our network, products, services, and Web sites;

  * Improving our services;

  * Notifications and provision of information about special offers and products or services available from us or our partners that may interest you;

  * Customization of your experience with Republic Wireless;

  * Solicitation of information from you, including through surveys, or administering contests or promotions;

  * Resolution of disputes and troubleshooting of other problems;

  * Prevention of potentially prohibited or illegal activities, or harm to any person or property;

  * Assisting law enforcement, pursuing or defending legal claims, and engaging in other compliance or legal activities;

  * Enforcement of our agreements with you, including our Terms of Service and our Acceptable Use Policy; and

  * As otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

We may use your information to help identify you as a user when you access our Web sites using different devices. If you use different devices (such as your home computer, laptop, and/or mobile device) to access our Web sites and/or engage in a transaction, we may be able to associate you with each of your devices. For example, if you choose to click the email link on a new device, we will be able to associate your current device with your account information. We may combine information we have collected from your use of different devices and use that information consistent with this Policy, such as to help provide a more personalized and consistent experience across your devices, and to deliver more relevant advertisements to you.

**How Do We Utilize Customer Proprietary Network Information?**

Some information related to certain communications services that we provide to you constitutes Customer Proprietary Network Information (“CPNI”). For example, CPNI includes to whom, where and when you make calls. Specific federal laws and regulations protect CPNI. We are committed to full compliance with these federal laws and regulations in all respects. We only will share or disclose your CPNI without your consent (i) to initiate, render, bill and collect for our telecommunications services provided to you; (ii) to protect you, Republic Wireless or other carriers from fraudulent or illegal use of, or subscription to, our products and services; (iii) to protect our rights or property; (iv) to provide your call location information in certain specified emergency situations, if applicable; (v) to market to you services or products among the categories of services or products to which you currently subscribe; and (vi) for other purposes permitted by law. You will receive a privacy notice regarding CPNI when you first contract for or order service and every two years thereafter. You may choose to opt out of the sharing of your CPNI within our family of companies (and their divisions) for certain marketing purposes. For more information regarding CPNI, please see [ _republicwireless.com/legal_](https://republicwireless.com/legal).

**How Do We Use Any Feedback You May Provide?**

Any anonymized data that you send to us such as your questions, suggestions, ideas or other creative material belongs to us and we will not treat it as confidential. We may adapt, disclose, display, distribute, reproduce, use, or create derivative works from any such information without acknowledgment of you or compensation to you.

**How Do We Share Your Information?**

Republic Wireless may share your information with others:

  * Within our family of companies (and their divisions) for operational purposes.

  * We may offer products or services with business partners, for example, customer financing from Affirm. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will appear either with ours or separately. If you choose to use these products or services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those business partners. We do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners and our Privacy Policy does not cover either these third parties or their information practices.

  * You can choose to access certain third party social media Web sites and services through our Web sites. When you do so, you share information with those sites and their privacy policies will govern the information you share with them. Our Privacy Policy does not cover either these third parties or their information practices. You may be able to modify your privacy settings with these third party social media Web sites.

  * We may use third party vendors to provide various services or functions on our behalf, including business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys, and fraud prevention. We may also authorize third-party vendors to collect information on our behalf to operate features of our Web sites or facilitate the delivery of online advertising tailored to your interests, among other reasons. Third-party vendors have access to and may collect information only as needed to perform their functions. We use a third-party intermediary to manage certain payment card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use billing information, including your billing name and address and credit card number, except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.

  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. We reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us in any such cases.

  * When we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of Republic Wireless, our community members, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements, subject to applicable law, including those governing the use and disclosure of CPNI.

  * To obtain a consumer report.

  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Except as described above, we will notify you when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information. We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors our Web sites receive.

**How You Can Update and Revise Your Information?**

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your information is relevant, accurate, and complete. Your use of our services or our Web site may permit you to update or revise your personal information through our Web site or otherwise from time to time. You also may contact us if you believe your information needs to be updated or revised.

**What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Collection and Use of Your Information?**

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information that we do not automatically collect, although it may be needed to take advantage of certain services or features offered on our Web sites.

  * You also can revise or update information as described above.

  * Whether registered as a Republic Wireless community member or not, you also may unsubscribe from promotional messages in any email we send. We reserve the right to send you other communications, including service announcements, administrative messages, and surveys relating to your Republic Wireless account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

  * Republic Wireless wants to make it easy for you to take advantage of opportunities on our Web sites. We do this by sending you email messages that contain information about your apparent communications-related interests. We believe these email messages will provide you with useful information about special offers available through our Web sites. You will have the opportunity to choose not to receive these email messages in any email we send.

  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your Web browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from Republic Wireless, you may not be able to access some tools, features, or portions of our Web sites. At this time our Web sites do not respond to “do not track” signals.

  * Certain ad networks have agreed to adhere to industry-supported consumer choice mechanisms, such as the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out for interest-based advertising, which can be found here: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/\\#!/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org//#!/).

  * The Digital Advertising Alliance also maintains a similar opt-out that may permit you to opt out of the use of your information to identify your devices across multiple websites. It can be found here: [http://optout.aboutads.info/\\#!/](http://optout.aboutads.info//#!/).

  * If we collect your device’s location when you use our mobile apps, we will ask your permission. Your phone’s location services settings permit you to control collection of your device location through our apps.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

While no company or Web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, we permit only authorized personnel to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions. We also employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information that we maintain. These measures include administrative safeguards, such as policies, procedures, and training, as well as physical and technical controls, such as encryption when personal information is transmitted across a website and where appropriate, for other transmissions, for example, certain information in cookies. However, we make no guarantee, representation or warranty that use of our services or Web sites is protected from all security threats, viruses, or other vulnerabilities or that your information always will be secure.

**How Do We Protect Children’s Privacy?**

The Web sites operated by Republic Wireless are general audience sites and do not offer services directed to children. If you believe an individual under age 13 has sent personal information to us, please notify us and we will delete or destroy such information as soon as reasonably possible.

**Does Our Privacy Policy Apply to External Links or Other Parties?**

If any part of our Web sites links you to other Web sites, those external Web sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. Similarly, if you choose to use services of another company about which we provided information, or due to your interaction with an ad or other content we provided, that party’s use of your information is not governed by this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**How Does Our Privacy Policy Apply If You Visit Our Web Sites from Outside the United States?**

Your information will be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States or other countries where our servers are located and where we operate. The data protection laws of the United States and other countries may vary from those applicable in your country. However, Republic Wireless will treat your information in compliance with law and as described in this policy regardless of the location from which it was collected. By using our Web site or services, you understand that your information may be transferred to us and to third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Do You Have Additional Rights Under California Law?**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email[ _info@republicwireless.com_](mailto:info@republicwireless.com).

**How Can You Contact Us?**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

**Mail:**

Republic Wireless, Inc.

Attention: Customer Care

Venture I

940 Main Campus Drive, STE 300

Raleigh, NC 27606

**Email:**

© 2018 Republic Wireless, Inc.

Effective January 3, 2018

Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
